<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gift certificate | Newborn photography</title><link>https://www.xn--vastsndinu-eeb.ee/en/tag/gift-certificate/</link><atom:link href="https://www.xn--vastsndinu-eeb.ee/en/tag/gift-certificate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>gift certificate</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2023 Viktoria Iljin</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 06:09:53 +0300</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://www.xn--vastsndinu-eeb.ee/media/sharing.jpg</url><title>gift certificate</title><link>https://www.xn--vastsndinu-eeb.ee/en/tag/gift-certificate/</link></image><item><title>A newborn photo shoot gift certificate - make priceless memories</title><link>https://www.xn--vastsndinu-eeb.ee/en/post/a-newborn-photo-shoot-gift-certificate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 06:09:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.xn--vastsndinu-eeb.ee/en/post/a-newborn-photo-shoot-gift-certificate/</guid><description>&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s not as simple as it looks to find a thoughtful newborn gift that the baby&amp;rsquo;s parents will like. Although baby goods stores today have an extraordinarily extensive selection, it can still be difficult to find exactly what new parents will enjoy and use.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Additionally, the newborn will outgrow any clothing, toys, or other items of a similar nature very fast because kids grow at an almost cosmic rate, therefore the ideal gift for such an occasion should be something that the family can truly cherish for years to come. In this situation, a gift certificate for a newborn photo session would be fantastic, and the whole family would love it.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure id="figure-newborn-photo-session-in-tallinn">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photo-session-1.jpg" alt="Newborn photo session in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Newborn photo session in Tallinn
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;h2 id="a-photo-shoot-gift-certificate-for-a-newborn-or-older-baby-is-the-ideal-baby-arrival-gift">A photo shoot gift certificate for a newborn or older baby is the ideal baby arrival gift.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A gift certificate becomes a truly valuable gift when the parents may decide when and under what conditions to use it. Others will find it more comfortable to employ a professional newborn photographer. Some families will undoubtedly prefer the baby&amp;rsquo;s first photo shoot to take place at home. Such flexibility is certainly conceivable, as are several possibilities for delivering finished photos, creating the baby&amp;rsquo;s first photo book, and other options, which are only constrained by the nominal amount of the gift certificate. The greatest amount of freedom in using a gift certificate makes it the ideal present for a family with a newborn baby, especially since the certificate&amp;rsquo;s validity can last up to a year.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure id="figure-newborn-photo-session-in-the-studio">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photo-session-2.jpg" alt="Newborn photo session in the studio" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Newborn photo session in the studio
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;h2 id="should-a-gift-for-a-babys-birth-be-a-surprise-or-not">Should a gift for a baby&amp;rsquo;s birth be a surprise or not?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>It is important to think carefully about whether you should surprise the parents with a gift for the arrival of the baby or if it would be better to let them know in advance that you would want to give them a gift certificate for a newborn photo shoot. There are various reasons why it is preferable to inform new parents of your wish in order to avoid uncomfortable circumstances.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You should first confirm that the family you intend to present your gift to is okay with having a photo session for their new baby. Even though this kind of photography is getting more and more common, many parents still choose not to take the very first images of their newborn because of customs and superstitions. A gift certificate in this situation will only result in disappointment.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The second reason is how the process is organized: if you want to make a surprise, the givers may decide to schedule their own newborn photo session with a different newborn photographer without being aware of your plan. Additionally, it is preferable to plan the date in advance with the preferred photographer to reduce the likelihood that the schedule will be full when the baby is delivered. It is therefore important to talk about such a birth gift in advance.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul class="cta-group">
&lt;li>
&lt;a href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/#contact" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="btn btn-primary px-3 py-3">Book newborn photo shoot&lt;/a>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>